chill.com 2012-06-20

# Privacy Policy | Chill

## Privacy Policy

### Last updated: March 16, 2012

Thank you for your interest in Namesake Inc. (“Namesake”), the Chill.com Service (the “Service”) and our website located at http://www.chill.com (the “Website”). Your use of the Service is subject to this Privacy Policy. We are pleased to provide this privacy policy to inform you of our practices with respect to how we collect and use personally identifiable information in connection with your use of the Service.

### Information We Collect

The data that we regularly collect about users of our Service (e.g., IP address, browser type, pages accessed, duration of visit, etc.) does not necessarily enable us to personally identify you, and that is not our intention. We do collect personally identifiable information about you, such as your name, email address, phone number, and location, when you voluntarily provide it by registering with us or using the Service. Once you become a user, you may provide additional information in your profile section. Providing additional information is optional. To facilitate your use of the Service, Namesake may automatically collect certain types of information when you access or use the Service. In order to collect this data, Namesake may utilize automated tools and files such as “cookies.” These automated tools and files may reside on our servers or on your computer or device. If you restrict our ability to use automated tools and files, your ability to access and use all or part of the Service may be limited or disabled completely.

### Use of Information

Namesake uses your personally identifiable information primarily to provide you with the Service and to provide customized content on the Service that is of interest to you. The information is also used to verify your authority to access the Service and to contact you when reasonably necessary. Namesake may also use any information you have provided as reasonably necessary to administer or provide customer support for the Service, and to provide you with periodic printed or e-mail communications about new products and services, discounts, special promotions or upcoming events. You may opt-out of receiving some or all non-Service related communications by updating your profile on the Service. Also, your full name and email address may be used when you use the Service to send a message to another user. Additionally, we use your email address to contact you on behalf of other friends on the site (such as when another user sends you a message or invites you to join a conversation).

### Controlling Your Personal Information

When you use our Service, all of the information that you submit, which may include name, email address, photographs and comments, will be publicly available to third parties and we may not have control over what they do with it. By using our Service, you consent to such disclosure. Namesake allows users to create and join conversations. You should be aware that when you voluntarily disclose personally identifiable information (e.g. user name, e-mail address) via conversations, forums, postings, profiles or other areas of the Website, that information, along with any substantive information disclosed in your communication, can be collected, correlated and used by third parties and may result in unsolicited messages from other posters or third parties. Such activities are beyond the control of Namesake. Please do not post any personal information on the Website or in other areas that you expect to keep private.

### Disclosure

Namesake may disclose your personal information to third parties from time to time in our sole discretion. For this reason you should not disclose information to Namesake that you do not want shared with third parties. In addition to the forgoing, Namesake will disclose your personally identifiable information as it believes is reasonably necessary to comply with law, regulation or other governmental authority or to prevent harm to yourself or others. Namesake may also contract with various third parties who help us provide and maintain the Service. For example, we may use a third party to process payments, and may subcontract out production, fulfillment, or other operations. In these cases, we will use commercially reasonable efforts to prevent such third parties from disclosing your personal information, except for the purpose of providing the services in question. Additionally, as part of the Service, Namesake will make your profile information available to other users of the Service. Finally, Namesake may disclose your personally identifiable information upon a transfer or sale to another entity of all or substantially all of Namesake’s stock or assets in Namesake’s line of business to which this Privacy Policy relates or upon any bankruptcy or other corporate reorganization.

### Links

For your convenience, we may provide links to certain third party websites or referrals to certain third parties’ products or services. If you choose to visit a third party’s website or use its products or services, please be aware that the third party’s privacy policy, and not the Namesake privacy policy, will govern your activities and any information you disclose while interacting with the third party.

### Security

Because any personally identifiable information you submit to Namesake is purely voluntary and should not be of a particularly sensitive nature, we employ our standard security measures with respect to this information and do not use special encryption methods at this time. Namesake user accounts are secured by user-created passwords. Please note that Namesake cannot guarantee the security of user account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of user information at any time.

### Collection of Information From Children

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information relating to children. In the event that we learn that we have collected personally identifiable information from anyone under 13 years of age without prior parental consent, we will take steps to promptly delete such information. By providing your personal information to Namesake, you represent that you are 13 years of age or older.

### Policy Changes

Namesake reserves the right to change this privacy policy, and will post any revisions on the Website. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes. Your continued use of the Service Website will be subject to the then-current privacy policy.

### International Visitors and Customers

The Namesake service and the Website is hosted in the United States. If you are visiting from the European Union (EU) or other regions with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from U.S. law, please note that you are transferring your personal data to the United States which does not have the same data protection laws as the EU and by providing your personal data you consent to:

  1. The use of your personal data for the purposes identified above in accordance with this Privacy Policy; and
  2. The transfer of your personal data to the United States as indicated above.

### No Error-Free Performance

Namesake does not guarantee error-free performance under this Privacy Policy. We may not always catch an unintended privacy issue, despite our efforts to do so. Accordingly, we welcome your feedback regarding any privacy concerns that you may have, including how we can improve this Privacy Policy. We will use reasonable efforts to comply with this Privacy Policy and will take prompt corrective action when we learn of any failure to comply with it.

### Legal Notices

This Privacy Policy is subject to the terms in our Terms of Use, available for review at http://www.chill.com/terms, including terms regarding limitations on damages, disclaimers of warranties, and resolution of disputes. Our Terms of Use take precedence over any conflicting provision in this Privacy Policy.

### Questions

If you have any questions about our privacy practices, please feel free to contact us at:

> Namesake, Inc.  
>  1431 Ocean Avenue  
>  Suite 1602  
>  Santa Monica, CA 90401  
>
